Guide to the Darrell C. Crain, Jr., presidential inaugural collection, 1817-1989 MS2035
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Inaugural medals, 1892-2009; MS2035 Series 10; 7.5 linear feet.
  - Inaugural Medals, George H.W. Bush, 1989 (Box 7, Item 5)
  - Inaugural Medals, George H.W. Bush, 1989 (Box 11, Item 14)
  - Inaugural Medals, George H.W. Bush, 1989 (Box 11, Item 15)
  - Inaugural Medals, William J. Clinton, 1993 (Box 7, Item 6)
    Gold, 21mm
  - Inaugural Medals, William J. Clinton, 1993 (Box 7, Item 7)
  - Inaugural Medals, William J. Clinton, 1993 (Box 7, Item 8)
  - Inaugural Medals, William J. Clinton, 1997 (Box 7, Item 9)
    Gold, 25mm
  - Inaugural Medals, William J. Clinton, 1997 (Box 7, Item 10)
  - Inaugural Medals, William J. Clinton, 1997 (Box 7, Item 11)
  - Inaugural Medals, George W. Bush, 2001-2009 (Box 7, Item 12)
  - Inaugural Medals, George W. Bush, 2001-2009 (Box 7, Item 13)
  - Inaugural Medals, George W. Bush, 2001-2009 (Box 7, Item 14)
  - Inaugural Medals, George W. Bush, 2001-2009 (Box 7, Item 15)
  - Inaugural Medals, George W. Bush, 2001-2009 (Box 7, Item 16)
  - Inaugural Medals, George W. Bush, 2001-2009 (Box 7, Item 17)
  - Inaugural Medals, George W. Bush, 2001-2009 (Box 7, Item 18)
  - Inaugural Medals, George W. Bush, 2001-2009 (Box 7, Item 19)
  - Inaugural Medals, George W. Bush, 2001-2009 (Box 7, Item 20)
  - Inaugural Medals, Barack Obama, 2009 (Box 7, Item 21)
  - Inaugural Medals, Barack Obama, 2009 (Box 7, Item 22)
  - Inaugural Medals, Barack Obama, 2009 (Box 7, Item 23)
  - George H. W. Bush and Barak Obama medals, 2005-2008; Series 10 (Box 8)
    Includes an Obama process set as well as several Obama medals and also some 2005 George H.W. Bush medals.